Welcome to Technical Mau
YouTube channel, a few days ago we
made a video on
how to get your bike insurance on ICICI Lombard, a lot of questions were asked by you people in it, to
answer those questions
we are making this video today because it is not
possible to answer everyone's questions
and along with that there are a lot of comments from you people about what is
behind it, like most of the comments are about what is
covered first or what will
we get in third party insurance, if
our vehicle meets with a white way accident then
how much will we get, how much amount will we not get,
you have many such questions, so
in this video I will tell all those questions
and also if you have not seen
this video on how to add two wheeler and join
this loot then you can definitely come and
check the video, the link will be found in the description,
you can check it by going to the playlist, the
title which is visible here, if you
enter the title also then you will get this
video,
so let's start the video, its
first day is short  A request, if you have
not yet subscribed to our channel, then
please subscribe so that you get the
uploading information of all the videos first, so first of all
I would like to clear this doubt of yours,
whether your policy is
of first party or third party, if you
take personal information in it, then in personal cover
you will get accidental insurance of Rs 1500000, there is
a condition of insurance in it, you will get the benefit of insurance,
if now you are the owner of the car, you
are the owner of your bike and you are also driving the bike
and you should have a license,
in this case it will be seen that if you have an
accident, then you will
get the benefit of insurance of Rs 15 lakh, this personal cover, the
same condition applies to the third party also,
it is not easy that the
rule of first party is different and the political rule is different,
now the most common question
of you people here was that in case of an
accident, the bike of the vehicle is
damaged here in Chhattisgarh Dhund, so what is the
first  What is the difference between first party and third
party insurance? So the most
complete difference in all these differences is
that in first party insurance, the
company gives you money according to the value of your bike,
but in first party it is exactly the
opposite of that, in this only your bike or
car will not be given, the third party, the third
person who is suffering loss from it, will
get it, there are two conditions in it, one is of
6000 in reverse in third party
and the other is limited, that is, there is a plan in this, the
latest plan of yours has come,
I will unmute it on the Telegram channel,
you can see the latest plan very
soon brother, there is only a difference of ₹100,
what is the planning by increasing the plan by that much, so
whatever loss the third person will have to bear, it will be borne by the
company, whatever
amount he has a little curve,
he will take it, till then the company will give only Rs.6000,
not more than that pack, oh these are the
concrete running on class time in third party, one is of Rs.784 and the other is of Rs.843
which  The 843 plan is the
best, in the 784 plan only the third person will
get Rs. 6000 only. So suppose the
third person has suffered a lot of damage, then that much will
not compensate him. So
while getting third party insurance, you should get the 843 plan. This
843 plan is applicable on
vehicles below 150 cc, which is
different according to different Cs.
You can see the list of all these if you want
or you can also check it online on CCEA mode. It is
not necessary that
you have got it done through ICICI. You
can get insurance from any company. There is no problem.
So now let us take you to the next
step. If you have got
insurance done through ICICI, then you get
an ICC application by taking care of it.
Install it and
register by entering the same number which you had given while making your drive, all your
policy details will be in your phone. If you are
going somewhere and the vehicle is being checked, then
you will not have to show the papers there.  If you do
n't need it, then this
was the detail related to your bike insurance, on
which you people got the maximum comments,
so we hope that you
liked this video a lot, if you liked it a lot,
please like it and if you have
any modern teachings, please ask by commenting, we will
meet in the next video, till then
bye-bye.